爸爸要我们继承他的事业
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀魔鬼
saving people, hunting things...
家族事业
the family business.
(绿河郡拘留中心)
上了11点新闻的银行劫匪是你 可不是我
You were the bank robber on the 11:00 news, not me.
- 喂 - 我是维克多·亨德里克森探员
- Yeah. - This is special agentvictor hendrickson.
我的任务是抓住你 不一定是活的
It's my jobto bring you in alive's a bonus but not necessary.
我已经找了你好几周了
I've been looking for you for weeks now.
还有 对 我也知道萨姆
And, yes, I know about sam, too.
我知道圣路易斯的凶杀案 还有你在巴尔的摩玩的小把戏
I know about the murder in st. Louis, thehoudini act you pulled in baltimore.
以及那些掘墓和盗窃
I know about the desecrations and the thefts.
我还知道你们的爸爸
I know about your dad.
你根本不了解我爸爸
You don't know crap about my dad.
咱们搞砸了
We are so screwed.
(现在)
(绿河郡拘留中心)
这就明白了
So, this makes a lot of sense.
他们先把这些囚室封闭 然后再打开
First, they close down this cellblock, andnow they open itback up again.
你交的税就是这么排上用场的
There's your tax dollars at work.
你准备好了吗
You got that ready.
是啊
Yes
我可不想被关进这儿来
Would hate to have gotten thrown in here.
嘿 你感觉到了吗
Hey, you feel that, man?
什么东西
Who is that?
嘿
Hey!
嘿 警卫 嘿
Hey, guard! Hey!
快点 伙计
Come on, man!
嘿 警卫
Hey! Guard!
快来人 嘿
Come here! Hey!
- 我去B区 又是兰德尔 - 明白
- Going down to "b" block.Randall again. - Copy that.
- 嘿 警卫 嘿 - 闭嘴
- Hey! Guard, hey! - Shut up
- 行了兰德尔 我还想睡觉呢 - 你没看见那东西
- Come on, randall, I'm trying to sleep. - You're telling me you didn'tsee that?
你没长眼吗 嘿
Are you blind?Hey!
- 兰德尔 安静 - 安静个屁 伙计
- Randall, cool it. - "Cool it, " my ass, man.
- 这外面有人 - 兰德尔 关灯睡觉
- There's somebody out there. - Randall, turn out your light and go to sleep.
我不想再说第二遍
I'm not gonna say it again.
- B区 熄灯 - 明白 熄灯
- Lights out, "b" block. - Copy that.Lights out
不
No.
不 不 不 不
No! No!No! No!
救命
Help!
不 不 不
No! No! No!
不 不 啊 不
No! No...!Aah! No...!
[邪恶力量 第2季第19集]
(3个月之后)
这边
This way.
- 我不喜欢这个计划 迪恩 - 是啊 我知道 你都说了很多遍了
- I hate this plan, dean. - Yeah, I got that the first 10 times I heard it.
别动
Freeze!
我说别动
I said, "freeze"!
双手放在脑后 跪下
Put your hands behind your head!Get down on your knees.
快
Now!
向前
To the front.
右转
To the right.
我管这叫霹雳蓝天使造型
I call this one the blue steel.
好 这就对了
Yeah, that's right.
好了 回队里去
Okay, back to the line up.
- 等等 我和尼克·诺特谁更帅 - 闭嘴
- Wait, who looks better, me or nick nolte? - Shut up.
来的正好 我想要奇士汉堡
Well, it's about time.I'll have a cheeseburger.
双份洋葱
Extra onions.
- 你觉得自己很幽默 - 我觉得自己挺可爱
- You think yo're fine. - I think I'm adorable.
终于能见到你很荣幸 迪恩
It is a pleasure tofinally meet you in person, dean.
我是维克多·亨德里克森探员 这是我的搭档雷迪探员
I'm special agentvictor hendrickson.This is my partner special agent reidy.
亨德里克森
Hendrickson.
- 不会是密尔沃基的那个亨德里克森吧 - 正是在下
- Not the milwaukee agent hendrickson. - Live and in person.
噢 拍的不错
Oh, nice shot.
等你到了安哥拉监狱 可以挂在自己的囚室里
You can hang that upin your cell at supermax.
也许我们可以忘记汉堡
Maybe we can just forget the cheeseburgers, huh?
噢 对了 继续装吧
Oh, yeah.Keep that game face on.
继续掩饰你有多心慌意乱
Try and cover up how cornered you are.
给他念念罪名
Read him the charges.
你被控邮件诈骗 盗用信用卡 还有盗墓
You got mail fraud, credit-card fraud.grave desecration.
直接说重点
Skip to the good ones.
持枪抢劫 绑架和 噢
Armed robbery, kidnapping, and, oh,
3件一级谋杀案
three counts of first-degree murder.
密尔沃基案件之后 你弟弟也成了谋杀案的嫌犯
And after milwaukee, your brother isnow a suspect in a murder case himself.
我得说 你们两个家伙
I'd say, for you two
"无恶不作"这词实在太便宜你们了
"screwed to hell"is a major understatement.
这个嘛 留得青山在 不怕没柴烧
Well, where there's life, there's hope, huh?
噢 这就是我四处抓你们的时候一直想的
Aw. See, that's what I kept thinking as I wassearching for your asses all over hell and gone.
你的爸爸把你们训练得不错
Your dad taught you well.
你们掩盖行踪的方法 还有在密尔沃基作案之后 你们
The way you cover your tracks, and, after milwaukee, the way you
就这么消失了
Vanished.
为了找到你们我差点没抓狂 问问他就知道了
Near went nuts trying to find you. Ask him.
他差点没抓狂
He near went nuts.
经过了这么多以后 你们却被一个探测器抓住
And after all of that, you gettripped upon a motion detector.
我得说这是非常小白的错误 我很…
Pretty rookie move.I got to say, I was...
惊讶
surprised.
- 迪恩·温彻斯特 - 正是本人
- Dean winchester? - In the flesh.
- 你是 - 玛拉·丹尼尔斯
- And you are? - Mara daniels.
公设辩护人办公室的
public defender's office.
我被分派到你和你弟弟的案子
I've been assigned you and your brother's case.
- 你是亨德里克森 - 对 我们还没完事
- Are you hendrickson? - Yeah, and we're not quite done here.
呃 是的 你已经没事了 如果不介意…
Uh, yeah, you are, and if you don't mind...
我想要和我的当事人谈谈 私下的
I would like to meet with my clients privately.
很不幸 你们破门而入的罪行
Unfortunatly, Your arraign menton the breaking-and-entering charge
要到周二才能被提审
won't be until tuesday.
- 他们会把我们关在郡监狱 - 没错
- They'll keep us in county jail? - That's right.
- 是绿河郡拘留所 - 对
- Green river county detention center? - Yes
考虑到你们被控的罪行
and considering the charges you're facing,
没有哪个神志正常的法官会批准保释
no judge in his right mind isgoing to grant you bail.
是啊 我们注意到了
Yeah, we figured that.
还有更多的案件从5个不同的州转过来
Extradition papers have already beenfiled from five separate states,
从密苏里和密尔沃基来的是最大的问题
missouri and wisconsin being the biggestconcern.
抢银行和谋杀
the bank robbery and the murder raps.
引渡能拖多久
How long can we stall extradition?
一周或更短
A week. Maybe less.
好了 快走
All right.Let's go.
继续前进
Go ahead.
你是我的了 宝贝儿
Your my , baby.
别担心萨姆 我保证不会拿你去换烟抽的
Don't worry, sam.I promiseI won't trade you for smokes.
我要头等舱
I call top bunk.
好吧
Okay.
我的室友不太爱说话 你的呢
My roommate doesn't say much.How's yours?
盯着我看个不停…
Just keeps staring at me...
不知怎么让我觉得很别扭
in a way that makes me really uneasy.
- 看来你交上新朋友了 - 迪恩…
- Sounds like you're making new friends. - Dean...
这事毫无疑问是 我们做过的最蠢最疯狂的事
this is, without a doubt, thedumbest, craziest thing we've ever done
在这么一个没完没了愚蠢又疯狂的活计里
and that's in a long, storied career of dumb and crazy.
- 冷静点 这都在计划之中 - 噢真的
- Calm down.It's all part of the plan. - Oh, really?
亨德里克森的出现也是计划之中
Hendrickson showing up was part of the plan?
对 那家伙不过比我想象的来得快了点
Yeah, that guy moves a little faster than I thought.
我们只需要找到这个鬼
All we got to do is find this ghost
把他放到 给自己来几个那种眼泪形状的纹身
put the sucker down, then grab ourselvesa couple of those tear drop tattoos.
一点不好笑
That's not funny.
迪恩 逃跑计划怎么样了
Dean, what about this escape plan?
万无一失 要不我早不干了
It's a sure thing. Iwouldn't have gone in if it wasn'T.
我是说 行了 这个地方显然是在闹鬼
I mean, come on, man.This placehas all the signs of a haunting.
- 无辜的人们死了 已经四个了 - 噢 可不 无辜的人们
- Innocent people are dead four so far. - Oh, yeah.Innocent.
怎么 难道你是刚从德克萨斯来的
What, are you from texas all of a sudden?
这些人进了监狱并不等于他们就该死
Just because these people are injail doesn't mean they deserve to die
如果我们不制止那家伙 还会有人死
and if we don't stop thisthing, people are gonna continue to die.
- 无论如何我们都干定这个活了 - 听着 迪恩
- We do the job wherever it takes us. - Look, dean.
跟我说实话 好吗
Just be straight with me, all right?
- 你接这活是为了迪肯 - 完全正确
- You're doing this for deacon? - Damn right.
可我们几乎不认识他
But we barely even know the guy.
我们知道他和爸爸一起服过役 救过爸爸的命 我们欠他的
We know he was in the corps with dad.We know he saved dad's life.We know we owe him.
是啊 好吧 可你不觉得他要求太高了
Yeah, all right.But don't youthink he's asking a little much?
无所谓
Doesn't matter.
也许我们不是什么圣人 但我们忠于职守 有恩必报
We may not be saints, but we'reloyal, and we pay our debts.
这对我来说很重要 对你也应该如此
Now, that means somethingto me, and it ought to to you.
老弟 我也不喜欢这案子
I'm not thrilled about this either, man,
可迪肯 要我们干掉这家伙
but deacon asked upto hunt this thing down.
我们就这么做
That's exactly what we're gonna do.
- 我说 这鸡肉还不错 - 太棒了 我吃完了
- You know, this chicken isn't half bad. - Great. Finish mine.
好吧 咱们来谈谈这案子 迪恩 一号嫌疑鬼是马克·穆迪 对吧
All right, so let's go backover this, dean.Spirit suspect number oneis mark moody, right?
对 超级变态杀手
Yeah, psycho killer extraordinaire
撒旦教徒 仪式杀人犯 死在监狱里
satanism, ritual murderer, died in jail.
- 你肯定是他干的 - 基本肯定
- You sure it's him? - Pretty sure.
迪恩 考虑到咱们现在的处境 "基本肯定"可不够好
Dean, considering our circumstances, I'mgonna need better than "pretty sure."
非常基本肯定
Really pretty sure.
穆迪死于心脏病 这也是这里所有受害者的死法
Moody diedof a heart attack, which iswhat all the victims in here are dying of.
他死在老囚室那边 30年前在他死后就关闭了
He diedin the old cellblock, which theyclosed after he croaked, 30 years ago.
现在他们重新打开作为备用 那也就是这些谋杀开始的时候
They just opened that backup.That's when the killings started.
你是说这个恶灵被释放出来了
So you think his spirit was released somehow?
可如果他已经被火化了呢
But what if he was already cremated?
我猜那老囚室里一定有什么东西 让他出现在这里
I'm guessing there's something in theold block that's keeping him around.
不管是什么 我们都得找到 然后 呃 后面的事你也知道 我吃完了
And whatever it is, we got to find it.And, uh, you know the rest.I'm done.
- 对不起 我… - 走路瞧着点
- Sorry. I... - watch where you're going.
好的 我只是…
Yeah. Sure.I just...
- 他已经道过歉了 - 迪恩…
- he said he was sorry. - Dean...
你跟我说话
you talking to me?
你是在跟我说话
Are you talking to me?
太棒了 又一个"出租车司机"的粉丝 对 我是在和你说话
Great, another guy who's seen"taxi driver"too many times.Yeah, I'm talking to you.
听我的 算了
Trust me.Let it go.
迪恩 好了
Dean, come on.
瞧 你就得这么跟那些家伙说话
See, that's how you got to talk to these guys.
马上就赢得尊敬
Instant respect.
你说什么来着
You were saying?
噢 好极了
Oh, great.
既然要动手就不要打脸和要害
We can end this right now. No harm, no foul.
够了
That's enough!
站起来 卢卡斯
On your feet, lucas.
是 长官 老大
Yes, sir, boss.
- 你叫什么名字 - 温彻斯特
- What's your name? - Winchester.
温彻斯特… 这可不是个好开头
Well, winchester...not a good start.
关禁闭
Solitary.
- 你也是 卢卡斯 - 是 长官
- You too, lucas. - Yes, sir.
玩的挺开心 对吧
Are we having fun yet, huh?
要是有个棒球就好了
I wish I had a baseball.
什么 你说什么
What?What'd you say?
我说"要是有个棒球就好了"
I said, "I wish I had a baseball."
- 你知道 就像史蒂夫·麦奎因 - 什么 史蒂夫·麦奎因
- You know, like like steve mcqueen. - Yeah?Steve Mcqueen
我想要个球棒 打瘪你的脑袋
Well, I wish I had a bat so Icould bash your fricking head in.
好吧
Okay.
好了 患难见真情的时刻结束了
Well, so much for the bonding in solitary moment.
见鬼
Crap.
卢卡斯 听我说 千万别动
Lucas, listen to me.Stay very still.
- 汗迪克森 - 嗨 丹尼尔斯
- Hendrickso-Hey, daniels. - Hendrickson
- 能和你谈谈吗 - 请坐
- Can I have a word? - Have a seat.
- 有什么事 - 我看过温彻斯特兄弟的案卷了
- What's on your mind? - I've been going through the winchester charges
我得说
and I got to say
- 有些奇怪的矛盾之处 - 欢迎光临我的世界
- there aresome weird in consistencies. - Welcome to my world.
我和巴尔的摩的一个警察谈过了 她发誓
I talked to a cop in balti more who swears up and down
这对兄弟救了她的命还帮她抓住凶手
these boys saved her life andhelped her catch a killer.
你负责的那件密尔沃基银行劫案的命
And there's a witness to your bank robbery in milwaukee.
一个目击者也说萨姆和迪恩救了她的命
She swears sam and dean saved her life.
- 从谁那儿救了她 - 关于那个 她有点记不清了
- Saved her from what? - She was a little unclear on that.
因为她脑子有病
That's because she's nuts.
听着 我当时就在密尔沃基 我和她谈过 和所有的证人都谈过
Look, I was in milwaukee.I spoketo her.I spoke to all the witnesses.
- 然后 - 然后
- And? - And
我只知道一点 不管这俩家伙去哪儿都有人死
all I know is, wherever these guys go, people die.
- 就这么简单 - 我不这么认为
- It's that simple. - I don't know that it is.
我并不那么肯定他们一定有罪
They just don't seem cut and dry guilty to me.
- 我觉得还有别的内情 - 比如什么
- I think there's more to this. - Like what?
不知道
I don't know.
我说不好
Can't put my finger on it.
只是…
It's just...
- 很奇怪 - 奇怪
- Strange. - Strange.
是啊 好了
Yeah. Okay.
大人们有事要办 所以…
Grown-ups are trying toget some work done here, so...
如果你不介意的话…
if you don't mind...
你好吗
How you doing?
我54岁 在一个窗户上都是铁栏杆的厕所擦地
I'm 54 years old, mopping the floorof a crapper with bars on the windows.
你觉得我好不好
How you think I'm doing?
好吧 破冰失败
All right.Bad icebreaker.
- 我叫萨姆 - 兰德尔
- I'm sam. - Randall.
很高兴见到你 兰德尔
Nice to meet you.Randall.
- 嘿 那个警卫死的那晚你是不是也在 - 对
- Hey, weren't you there the night that guard died? - Yeah.
发生什么了
Well, what happened?
- 他们说是工作压力 - 是吗
- They say the stress of the job got him. - Yeah?
那你怎么说
What do you say?
你管这事干嘛 小子
Why are you inside, kid?
因为我有个笨蛋老哥
Because I got an idiot for a brother.
- 好理由 - 是啊
- That'll do it. - Yeah.
这地方没那么糟 比起老囚室那边 这里简直算是希尔顿酒店了
Well, this place aingt so bad.Compared tothe old cellblock, this is the damn hilton.
- 你还在老囚室那边呆过 - 噢 当然 我可是个常客
- You spent time in the old block? - Oh, yeah, I was a regular customer.
- 马克·穆迪不是也关在那儿 - 他是被关过那儿
- Didn't they have mark moody there for a while? - He was there.
那个疯子死的那天晚上 我也在
I was there, too, the night that lunatic bought it.
是吗 听说是心脏病发作
Yeah?It was a heart attack, right?
当然 他的心脏在警卫拿他的脑袋 做挥棒练习之后就停了
Sure, his heart stopped right after the guardstopped using his head for batting practice.
第二天早上 我清理他囚室里的血迹 简直一团糟
The next morning, I was in hiscell, mopping up the blood.What a mess.
等等 这么说他… 他是被活活打死 却没人上报
Wait. So he... he was beatenand nobody reported it?
闭上你的嘴 除非你想死于同样的心脏病 明白
You kept your mouth shut, unless you wantedto die from the same heart attack, you know?
兰德尔 现场到底有多少血迹
Randall, exactly how much blood was there?
- 我跟 - 三个A
- Call. - Three aces.
这就是爆冷门
That's a bad beat.
确实是惨痛一击 但我是…
That is a bad beat, but, see, I'm full...
也是三个A
3s over aces.
抱歉 游戏规则如此 老兄
Sorry.Hey, it's a cruel game, my friend.
抱歉 老兄
Sorry, guys.
- 这也太容易了 - 你根本不抽烟
- It's like picking low-hanging fruit. - You don't even smoke.
这在监狱里能当钱用
This is the currency of the realm.
- 听着 我打听到了穆迪的事情 - 我也是
- Look. I got a good lead on moody. - Me too.
- 他的灵魂昨晚还来看了看我 - 什么
- His spirit paid a little visit last night. - What?
表停了 灯在闪 冷得很 我是说 他该做的都做了
The clock stopped, the flickering lights, coldspot...I mean, he did everything but yell boo.
- 哦 怎么回事 - 他从我面前走过
- Well, what happened? - He walked right by me.
从那声惨叫来看卢卡斯没那么幸运
Lucas wasn't so lucky.I mean, the way he was screaming...
他是很混 但也不该那样惨死
guy was a jerk, but hedidn't deserve to go like that.
穆迪那你发现什么
What'd you find out on moody?
我想或许能在他牢房里找到
Yeah, I think I know where wemight find his remains
- 残留的血迹 血迹 - 我还以为是死于心脏病
- blood in his old cell. - The blood?I thought it was a heart attack.
记录是的 是狱警伪造的
It was, after the guards worked him over.
现场血迹多得拖了半天
There was so much bloodin there, they had trouble mopping it out.
- 我们怎么进去 - 我有个计划
- How we gonna get in? - I got a plan.
智多星萨姆 我就知道
That's the sammy I know.
你就像克林特·伊斯特伍德的"逃出亚卡拉"
You're likeclint eastwood from "escape from alcatraz."
问题是 就算找到血迹怎么烧毁
Problem is, if we find something, how are we gonna burn it?
没有然烧剂
We don't have any accelerant.
问得好 我有"大逃亡"里的詹姆斯·加纳的技术
Good thing I'm like jamesgarner from "the great escape."
嘿 伙计们 谁想做个交易
Hey, fellas!Who's ready to deal?
- 这样能行吗 - 基本能行
- You sure about this? - Pretty sure.
哦 鉴于我们身处的环境 "基本能行" 可不行
Yeah, well, considering our circumstances, I'd like a little better than "pretty sure."
那好 真的基本能行
Okay...really pretty sure.
我要有点嚼劲的
I'd like mine al dente.
好极了
Perfect.
在等餐后甜点 泰尼
Save room for dessert, tiny.
嘿 我想问你 因为我没法不注意你那2吨的身材
Hey, I wanted to ask you, becauseI couldn'thelp but notice that you are two tons of fun.
只是好奇 这是甲状腺问题 还是一些自卑的问题
Just curious...is it likea thyroid problem, oris it some deep sea ted self esteem issue?
因为 你知道 他们只是甜甜圈
Because, you know, they're, uh...they're just dough nuts.
不是爱人
They're not love.
伙计们 帮把手
Guys, give me a hand.
我们晚来一步你就挂了
If we'd waited any longer, you'd be dead.
你们来的可真早
You waited long enough.
为了你自己 不许回嘴
Do yourself a favor.Don't talk.
把他们都带到医务室
Take them both up to the infirmary.
- 嘿 泰尼 - 什么
- Hey, tiny. - Yeah?
抱歉之前那样说你
Hey, sorry about the things I was saying earlier.
无法解释但我必须惹毛你
Can't really tell you whybut I had to get you angry.
所以 嗯…
So, uh...
- 无论如何 抱歉 - 没关系
- anyway, sorry. - It's okay.
事实是我确实自卑
Truth is, I have low-self-esteem issues.
我老爸经营露天煤矿 哥哥不务正业
My old man treated meand my brother like crap,
直到爸爸死前才悔改
right up till the day he died.
- 他怎么死的 - 我哥枪杀了他
- How'd he die? - My brother shot him.
这样啊
Okay.
- 哦 糟糕 - 怎么了
- Oh, crap. - What is it?
怎么回事
What is going on?
发生什么了
What is it?
- 哦 不 不 - 泰尼 泰尼
- Oh! No! No! - Tiny! Tiny!
警卫
Guard!
等等 你说不是穆迪干的
Wait. So you're telling me it wasn't moody?
除非他喜欢扮成护士
Not unless he liked goingaround dressed like a nurse.
- 可怜的泰尼 大块头泰尼 - 等等 那这 这是
- Poor tiny, man.Poor giant tiny. - Wait, so this is...this is, like
- 在这工作的护士的灵魂 - 我不知道 我猜是
- the ghost of some nurse who worked here or something? - I don't know, man.I guess.
在这一点上 "我不明白"这和我有什么关系
At this point, "I don'tknow"isn't working for me.
知道吗 我以为这儿的工作结束了 我和迪肯 说了
See, uh, I thought we were done.I called Deacon.It's happening.
我们今晚就走
We're getting out tonight.
那我们就要赶紧查查了
I guess we got to do some quick research, then.
怎么查 我是说 或许你没注意
How?I mean, maybe you haven't noticed...
我们在监狱里
we're in jail.
你想知道护士的情况
You want to know about some nurse?
- 你为什么想知道 - 我们自有原因
- Why you want to know? - We got our reasons,
但是 嗯 和我们说说绝对值得
but, uh, we'll make it worth your while.
那么 这个护士 灰白色头发 一只眼睛有问题 你想起来没
So, this nurse, she would have white hair, onescrewed-up eye...is that ringing a bell?
- 是的 是的 我记得她 - 你记得名字吗
- Yeah.Yeah, I remember her. - You remember her name?
不 还有点模糊
No, that's still kind of fuzzy.
给他
Give it to him.
- 我赚来的 - 迪恩
- I earned these. - Dean.
格洛克纳 格洛克纳护士 70年代在这工作的讨厌的老女人
Glockner...nurse glockner.Nasty old bitch worked here in the '70s.
- 你认识她 - 见过一次
- You knew her? - I met her once.
去打破伤风 她对着我的胳膊就是猛的一戳
Had to geta tetanus shot.She damnnear jabbed the needle through my arm.
- 至少我还活着 - 你什么意思
- At least I got out of there alive. - What do you mean?
我听过不少传言 真假就难说了
I've heard these stories.Idon't know if they were true.
- 囚犯是个大嘴巴 但我们的话不太可信 - 什么传言
- Cons love to talk, but we're all liars. - What kind of stories?
人们经常因感冒走进去 之后就被裹尸袋抬出来了
Guys would go up with a cold.Next thing you know, they're in a body bag.
都是心脏病猝发 无论老少
A whole rash of heart attacks...young guys, old guys.
- 心脏病 - 是的
- Heart attacks? - Yeah.
说是格洛克纳痛恨囚犯
The story was glockner had it out for cons
只是用针头代替了刀枪
and she did this, uh, charlesbronson thing with a hypodermic.
总之是传言而已 没人去证实
Anyway, that was the rumor.Nobody ever proved anything.
- 格洛克纳怎么了 - 我不知道
- Whatever happened to glockner? - I don't know.
我打完针就走了 之后我再去她已经不在了
I finished my bitand left.Next timeI landed back in here, she was gone.
那好 我们假设关于格洛克纳的事都是真的
Okay, so let's say thosestories on glockner were true.
只是一种说法
It's a thought.
- 活着时她是个警员 死后还认为是 - 没错
- In life, she's a vigilante.In death, same thing. - Right
但是她怎么会被禁锢在旧牢房中
but how is she tied in with the old cellblock?
而且如果她的目标是囚犯 为什么要杀死警卫
And if she's going aftercons, why kill that one guard?
我倒是听说那个警卫不太清白
I did hear in the yard that thatguard wasn't exactly squeaky clean, so
或许她所有犯法的人都是她的目标 比如我
maybe she's going after anybodythat breaks a law, like me.
- 你在院子里也听见了 - 没错
- You heard in the yard? - Yeah.
迪恩 你怎么能把监狱都当自己家一样
Does it bother you at allhow easily you seem to fit in here?
没有 才没有
No, not really.
那好 无论如何 我们要再去调查格洛克纳
All right. Either way, weneed more info on glockner.
如果她被埋葬了 如果是的话在哪
If she's buried...if so, where?
我们有5个小时去调查
And we got five hours to get it.
别 别给我那副 "我们得解决这件事"的表情
No, no.Don't give me that "we gotto see this thing through" look.
无论如何我们今晚就走
We are leaving tonight, no matter what.
我不想令迪肯 失望 我们欠他的
I don't want to let Deacon down.We do owe him.
确实 但也不用搭上你我的性命 迪恩
Yeah, but we don't owe him our lives, dean.
你去哪儿
Where you going?
去找我们的律师
I'm gonna go talk with our lawyer.
- 你想让我做什么 - 她叫格洛克纳
- You want me to what? - Her name was glockner.
70年代在这里做护士
She worked here as a nurse in the '70s.
我要你找到和相关的一切 但最重要的是
I need you to find out everything youcan about her but, most importantly
- 她怎么死的 埋在哪里 - 你疯了
- how she died and where she's buried. - Are you nuts?
不记得自己惹上大麻烦了
Do you have any idea the kind of trouble you're in?
- 知道一点 - 那好
- I have a vague notion. - Good
那就别理什么护士谈谈你们的案子
so let's forget about some randomnurse and talk about your case.
- 玛拉 你叫玛拉 对吧 - 是的
- Mara...it's mara, right? - Yeah.
我知道你想帮我
I get that you're trying to help me.
很清楚 但相信我 照我的话做才能真正帮到我
I do, but believe me when I say thatthis is the best way that you can help.
- 是吗 怎么可能 解释一下 - 真希望我能 可惜不能
- Really? How?Explain that to me. - I wish I could, but I can'T.
我只是请求你相信我所说的话
I'm just gonna have toask you to trust me on this.
我为什么要相信
Why should I?
- 亨德里克森说你们俩是怪物 - 我是怪物
- Hendrickson says you're a monster. - I'm a monster?
哦 他说错了 知道吗
Well, h-he's wrong, okay?
我和他说的不一样
I'm not what they say I am.
- 人人都这么说 - 是吗
- Everybody says that. - Yeah.
如果你和我想象中的一样聪明
If you're as smart a P.D.As I think you are,
你就可以一眼看出你的当事人是否有罪 就这样
then you can tell with just one look whetheror not your clients are guilty, just like that.
我想叫你看着我 认真的看
So I want you to look at me, really look,
告诉我 我像罪犯吗
and you tell me...am I guilty?
我们不是坏人
We're not the bad guys.
- 她答应去查了 - 没 还没这么快
- Did she go for it? - No. No, not so much.
- 或许她还在犹豫 - 我们可等不了她
- But maybe she'll still come around. - We can't wait to find out.
- 我们再待一天 - 不 不 不 今晚就走 没得商量
- We could give it another day. - No, no, no. We're leaving tonight, and that's it.
- 那就眼看着人们死去 - 别这么说 好吗
- So we're just gonna let these people die? - Don't give me that, all right?
你定了这个愚蠢的计划 我执行而已 现在已经有麻烦了
This was your stupid plan.I went alongwith it, but we're sticking to the plan.
那好 你走我留下
Okay.Uh, you leave.I'm gonna stay.
- 别走 不要离开我 - 去你的
- Don't turn away.Don't turn away from me. - Screw you.
什么 去你的
What?Screw you!
那好 硬骨头 普通的方法对付不了你们
All right, hard case.I see the usualmethods aingt gonna work with you.
你也是 甜心
You too, sweetheart.
出去
Take off.
我单独来解决
I want to handle this alone.
迪肯 你可打我我够呛 老兄
Deacon, you are beating the holy hell out of me, man.
抱歉 迪恩
Sorry, dean.
我以为我们很默契
I thought I was going easy on you.
- 只是 嗯 想演的逼真点 - 是啊 演出结束
- Just, uh, trying to make it look real. - Yeah. Well, mission accomplished.
- 多谢 - 事情完了
- Thanks. - So, is it over?
- 不 情况有变 不是穆迪 - 是吗
- No.Turns out, it wasn't moody. - What?
- 是的 - 那是谁
- Yeah. - Then who?
嗯 我们觉得是曾在这工作的某个护士 但还不能肯定
Uh, we think it's some nurse who used towork here, but we're shy on all the intel.
所以我们还要逗留几天 直到确定
Which is why we should stick around.Until we find it.
- 哦 伙计们 - 你不是来真的吧 迪恩
- Oh, hey guys. - You want to have this fight for real, dean?
我们得走 现在就离开
We got to go.We've got to go now!
- 你们 - 必须得走 迪恩
- Guys. - We are leaving dean.
否则我们会带着手铐 和亨德里克森一起去密尔沃基
Otherwise, we'll be leaving in shacklesfor milwaukee, with hendrickson as company.
- 哦 别这样 - 你们听我说
- Oh, come on. - Guys!
- 什么 - 什么
- What? - What?
你们的律师留下这个
Your lawyer left this for you.
看见了吧 我用温柔打动了她
Would you look at that. Man, I am freaking velvety smooth.
你可能做梦想过 打开看过再自夸不迟
You want to, maybe, open it up afteryou're done patting yourself on the back?
那好
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 哦 - 什么 不想给我们看看 迪恩
- Wow. - What?You want to share with the class, dean?
格洛克纳死在穆迪的旧牢房
Glockner died in theold cellblock after moody bit it.
似乎邻里间不大和睦
Seems they had a little inmate uprising.
而她被牵涉之中
she got caught in the middle.
他们把她扶到单间 大脑严重水肿
They dragged her to a solitary cellgave hera severe cerebral edema.
- 有人殴打她 - 没错
- Someone bashed her head in. - Yeah.
- 说了埋在哪里吗 - 是的
- Does it say where she's buried? - Yep.
那好 该送你们出去了
All right, then, let's get you the hell out of here.
别担心 迪肯 我们会解决的
Don't worry, Deacon.We'll get rid of this thing.
好极了 我可不想监狱里有鬼魂
Good, because I want it out of my prison.
孩子们 嗯…
Boys, uh...
我不知道怎么感激你们好
I can't thank you enough for this.
我知道要求很过分但你们还是来了
I know it was asking a lotbut you still came through.
你们父亲培养出了好儿子
Your daddy raised you right.
- 哦 我们欠你的 - 那好
- Well, we owed you. - Right.
- 希望有机会再见 嗯 - 千万别在这里 好吗
- Hope to see you again, huh? - Just not in here, okay?
哦 我们尽量
Yeah, we'll do our best.
哦…
Oh...
- 你想打哪 - 什么
- where do you want it? - What?
明白 嗯…
Yeah, um...um...
要动真格
make it look real, son.
哦 老兄 你真是长有一对猫眼
oh, man, are you a sight for sore eyes.
知道吗 真希望看看亨德里克森的表情
You know, I almost wish Icould see hendrickson's face.
真的 不见他我会更高兴
Really?Because I'd be happy ifI never saw him again.
- 我们还没真正脱险 迪恩 知道吗 - 是啊
- We're not really out of the woods yet, dean, you know? - Yeah.
说得好
Good point.
我说过了 其中一人走到我身后
I told you.One of them came up behind me.
- 你被他们打昏了 - 是的
- You let them get the drop on you. - Yeah.
我搞砸了 行了吧 你还想让我说什么
I screwed up, all right?What do you want me to say?
我想知道他们去哪
I want to know where they're headed.
- 我怎么会知道 - 那重新来过
- How the hell would I know? - Let's start over again.
- 看在上帝的分上 - 再来
- For god's sake. - Again
我要知道他们今天所作的一切 从起床开始
I want to know everything they didtoday, from the minute they woke up.
起床…
Got up...
吃早餐 探访时间 活动时间
breakfast, visiting hours, rec time.
- 什么人探访 - 只有律师
- Any visitors? - Just their lawyer.
问题很简单 你和迪恩说了些什么
It's an easy question.What did you and Dean talk about?
我已经说过了 这是我和当事人之间的私人谈话
I have already told you.It was a privateconversation between me and my client.
是啊 3小时候他就逃跑了
Right, and three hours laterhe just happened to bust out.
告诉我 他说过什么
Now, tell me what he said.
我们得快点 如果亨德里克森去问律师…
We got to move it.Ifhendrickson gets to the lawyer...
我想她什么也不会说
I thought she couldn't say anything.
知道吗 律师和当事人的谈话受法律保护之类的
you know, that whole lawyer-client-privilege thing.
- 你没申请保护 迪恩 - 那她就会说了
- The privilege doesn't apply, dean. - So she'll talk?
她必须说
She has to.
变态法律
That's freaking super.
我们这样说吧
Let me make this simple.
你不说就是协助疑犯逃跑
You don't come clean, I will put youon the hook for aiding and abetting.
- 太荒唐了 - 你以为我不会
- That is ridiculous. - You don't think that I can?
你以为我在耍询问技巧 女士
You think this is some kind of game, lady?
你可惹不起我
I am the last person you want to screw with.
现在 告诉我…
Now, tell me...
他说了什么
what he said.
他叫我去做调查
He wanted me to do some research...
- 一个死于1976年的监狱护士 - 什么 为什么
- ...on a prison nurse that died in 1976. - What? Why?
- 我不知道 - 还有什么
- I don't know. - What else?
- 他们想知道她被埋在哪里 - 你查到了
- They wanted to know where she was buried. - Did you find out where?
- 是的 - 你告诉他们了
- Yeah. - Did you tell them?
是的
yeah.
告诉我
Tell me.
(半山公墓)
挖到她了
Got her.
你放走了他们
You let those two go.
你确定是这个墓地
Are you sure this is the right damn cemetery?
她说半山 半山公墓
She said mountainside...mountainside cemetery.
(绿谷公墓)
- 之前以为我们搞砸了 - 是啊 我知道
- thought we were screwed before? - Yeah, I know.
- 我们以后要低调点儿 - "低调" 迪恩
- We got to go deep this time. - "Deep, " dean?
我们该去也门
We should go to yemen.
哦 我… 可还没准备那么低调
Oh, I'm...not sure I'm ready to go that deep.